Finding Aid for the David L. Carlton Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
David L. Carlton Papers
circa 1970s-2010s
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0943
22.5 linear_feet
- History 278a-Syllabus, etc. (Box 1)
- "History of Appalachia" History 278 (Box 1)
- History 278-Transparencies (Box 1)
- History 291/Econ 245-History of American Enterprise (Box 1)
- History 294 (Box 1)
- History 295-Syllabus, etc. (Box 1)
- History 295 (Box 1)
- History 297-Senior Honors Seminar (Box 1)
- History 300 (Box 1)
- History 378a (Box 1)
- History 378a (Box 1)
- History 378b (Box 1)
- History Department Enrollments (Box 1)
- Southern History Collection Consulting Committee (Box 1)
- Serial Recommendation Forms (Box 1)
- Media Fellowship on Southern Culture-VV (Box 1)
- James Agee Film Project (Box 1)
- John Adler-Harper's Weekly Project (Box 1)
- Library Bibliographer Search (Box 1)
- Library Exceptions Funding (Box 1)
- Library Exceptions Funding (Box 1)
- Library Committee (Box 1)
- Department Lectures Committee (Box 1)
- Qualifying Exams-Drafts + Copies (Box 1)
- Graduate Students-General (Box 1)
- Graduate Programs-Misc. Corresp. (Box 1)
- History Graduate Reading List (Top Forty) (Box 1)
- Graduate Placement (Box 1)
- PBK Triennial, Chicago (Box 1)
- VU History Department-External Review (Box 1)
- Survey Reform Committee (Box 1)
- History Department Retreat (Box 1)
- Igarash: Revieew Meeting-Minutes (Box 1)
- Don Doyle Promotion Committee (Box 1)
- Library Exceptions Committee (Box 1)
- Beth Rose-Revieew (Box 1)
- VU History Department-Senior Search (Box 1)
- Junior US Search (Box 1)
- US Womens History Search (Box 1)
- US Diplomatic Search (Box 1)
- Undergraduate Studies + Honors Committee (Box 1)
- VU Southern Studies Program-W Ferris (Box 1)
- Social Sciences Subcommittee, CPC (Box 1)
- RPW Fellows Program (Box 1)
- Phi Beta Kappa Nominating Committee (Box 1)
- Graduate School Admissions & Financial Aid (Box 2)
- Graduate Admissions (Box 2)
- Graduate Program in History (Box 2)
- US Search (2) (Box 2)
- Omnibus US Search (Box 2)
- VUCept (Box 2)
- Seminar Workshop (Box 2)
- Writing Workshop (Box 2)
- American Studies 201-Lecture Notes (Box 2)
- History 278-Lecture Notes (Box 2)
- History 171b-Stuff (Misc.) (Box 2)
- History 278a+b-Term Paper Guidelines (Box 2)
- History 200 (Box 2)
- American Studies Syllabi (Box 2)
- History 295-(illegible) Recons.-Syllabus (Box 2)
- History 273-Tests (Box 2)
- History 273-Syllabus (Box 2)
- History 191 (Box 2)
- History 115w-Syllabus (Box 2)
- History 171-Syllabus (Box 2)
- History 278b-Lecture Notes (Box 2)
- History 278b-Handouts (Box 2)
- History 278b-Tests (Box 2)
- History 278a-Tests (Box 2)
- Unlabeled (Box 2)
- History 278a-Handouts (Box 2)
- George B. Tindall (Box 3)
- Edgar T. Thompson (Box 3)
- George D. Terry (Box 3)
- Eugene TeSelle (Box 3)
- Tom E. Terrill (Box 3)
- Richard Sylla (Box 3)
- Stephen W. Taylor (Box 3)
- Scott Strickland (Box 3)
- Allen H. Stokes (Box 3)
- Richard Stockel (Box 3)
- Manisha Sinka (Box 3)
- George Sims (Box 3)
- Anastasia Sims (Box 3)
- Bryant Simon (Box 3)
- Donald R. Shriver (Box 3)
- Michael Shirley-Tenure Review (Box 3)
- Michael Shirley (Box 3)
- Sam Shannon (Box 3)
- Jack Roper (Box 3)
- James L. Roark (Box 3)
- Roger L. Ransom (Box 3)
- Joseph Pratt (Box 3)
- Larwrence N. Powell (Box 3)
- William H. Phillips (Box 3)
- Elizabeth Perry (Box 3)
- Martin L. Oliff (Box 3)
- Michael O'Brien (Box 3)
- Robert J. Norrell (Box 3)
- Dale Newman-Papers + Evaluation (Box 3)
- Joe Mount (Box 3)
- David Moltke-Hansen (Box 3)
- Randall Miller (Box 3)
- William Moss (Box 3)
- Sam McSeverey (Box 3)
- Robert C. McMath (Box 3)
- Terry McIntosh (Box 3)
- Cathy L. McHugh (Box 3)
- Peyton McCrary (Box 3)
- Kenneth Lipotito (Robert Gallman) (Box 3)
- Jan Lewis (Box 3)
- Cliff Kuhn (Box 3)
- Mark Kruman (Box 3)
- Michael Kohl (Clemson) (Box 3)
- Rachel Klein (Box 3)
- Richard H. King (Box 3)
- Robin D. G. Kelley (Box 3)
- Charles Joyner (Box 3)
- Michael P. Johnson (Box 3)
- Dale Johnson (Box 3)
- James A. Hodges (Box 3)
- J. Leo'n Helguera (Box 3)
- Hugh H. Hawkins (Box 3)
- Gordon Harvey (Box 3)
- Joel Harrington (Box 3)
- Jacqueline Hall (Box 3)
- Steve Hahn (Box 3)
- Larry J. Griffin (Box 3)
- Dewey Wesley Grantham Memorial (Box 3)
- Hugh D. Graham (Box 3)
- Eugene D. Genovese (Box 3)
- Eugene Genovese (Box 3)
- Gary R. Freeze (Box 3)
- Paul Freedman (Box 3)
- Betsey Fox-Genovese (Box 3)
- Jimmie L. Franklin (Box 3)
- Student Letters (Box 4)
- Letters of Reference (Box 4)
- Advisees (Box 4)
- Letters of Reference (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 4)
- Reserve Room Requisitions (Box 5)
- MLK Series (Box 5)
- Colonial Dames Award (Box 5)
- Economic History Association (Box 5)
- Wm. Clements Center for SW Studies (Box 5)
- VU University Library Committee (Box 5)
- Country Music Hall of Fame Internship (Box 5)
- VU Religious Affaairs Committee (Box 5)
- David Harmon (AL Public TV) (Box 5)
- Millenial Gathering of Writers of the New South (Box 5)
- "The American South + the American Manufacturing Belt" (Box 5)
- Subcommittee on History + Culture (Box 5)
- The Teaching Company (Box 5)
- "The Problem With Outsourcing" (Box 5)
- History and Culture (Box 5)
- MLK Committee (Box 5)
- Southern Festival of Books (Box 5)
- Me In The News (Box 5)
- Appalachia Talk-Alternative Spring Break (Box 5)
- Economics + History-Learning Outcomes Assessment (Box 5)
- VU Psychological + Counseling Center (Box 5)
- Teaching American History-ETSU (Box 5)
- Alternative Spring Break (Box 5)
- Henry M. Littlefield "The Wizard of Oz" Parable on Populism" (Box 5)
- F.J. Tuner, "The Significance of the Frontier in American History" (Box 5)
- Vivien G. Fyrd, Art +Empire, Ch. 5 (Box 5)
- Ron Eller-"Appalachian History" Notes (Box 5)
- History 171a-Transparencies (Box 5)
- History 171a-Lectures (Box 5)
- History 171b-Lecture Notes (Box 5)
- History 277-Transparencies (Box 5)
- ΦBK Executive Council (Box 6)
- Unlabeled (Box 6)
- MLK-Garrow Talk (Box 6)
- History + Culture Subcommittee (Box 6)
- History + Culture Subcommittee (Box 6)
- History + Culture Subcommittee (Box 6)
- History + Culture Subcommittee (Box 6)
- History + Culture Subcommittee (Box 6)
- History + Culture Subcommittee (Box 6)
- History + Culture Subcommittee, CPC (Box 6)
- American Studies Search Committee (Box 6)
- American Studies Search Committee (Box 6)
- University Research Council (Box 6)
- Commencement (Box 6)
- Action Research (Box 6)
- College of A+S-Curriculum Committee (Box 6)
- Computer Purchase Plan (Box 6)
- Arts + Science Memos (Box 6)
- Vanderbilt University (Box 6)
- VIPPS (Box 6)
- URC-Social/Science Sucommittee (Box 6)
- Sponsored Research (Box 6)
- VU Residential Programs (Box 6)
- VU-Policies (Box 6)
- Vanderbilt News - Public Affairs (Box 6)
- MLK Series (Box 6)
- James D. Anderson (MLK Lecture) (Box 6)
- VU Learning Resource Center (Box 6)
- Graduate Faculty Delegate Assembly (Box 6)
- Elder Hostel (Silvine Hudson) (Box 6)
- Leave Application (Box 6)
- E. Gordon Gee (Box 6)
- S.H.A.-New Orleans (Box 7)
- SHA Program Committee (Box 7)
- Southern Historical Association-1997 Meeting (Box 7)
- Southern Historical Association Meeting, Forth Worth (Box 7)
- S.H.A.-Ft. Worth [see also Buenger file] (Box 7)
- Southern Historical Association Meeting-New Orleans (Box 7)
- S.H.A. Meeting-Houston, November 1985 (Box 7)
- "Colonial Economy" (Box 7)
- Southern Historical Association (Box 7)
- Southern Festival of Books (Box 7)
- Spuithern Association of Women Historians (Box 7)
- South Carolina Encyclopedia (Box 7)
- Sons of Confederate Veterans (Box 7)
- SHOT Meeting, Atlanta, Oct. 2003 (Box 7)
- Watson-Brown Foundation (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society - Meeting (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society - Meeting (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society, June 2002 (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society-Brooks Forum (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society - Meeting (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society - Dissertation Session - Meeting (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society Dissertation Session, 1997 Meeting (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society-Dissertation Session, 1996 Meeting (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Soc.-Diss. Session (Box 7)
- St. George Tucker Society (Box 7)
- "Southern Textiles in Global Context"-SIP (Box 7)
- SIP 2003-Nashville (Box 7)
- Southern Industrialization Project-St. Louis, May 2002 (Box 7)
- Southern Economic History Conference (Box 7)
- SHEAR Meeting, July 18-21, 1996 (Box 7)
- Social Science History Association, Nov 2008 (Box 7)
- SSHA-Portland, OR, Nov. 2005 (Box 7)
- SSHA-2002 Meeting (Box 7)
- Social Science History Association, Oct. 2002 (Box 7)
- Social Science History Association Meeting (Box 7)
- Social Science History Association, 1995 Meeting (Box 7)
- Social Science History Association, Nov 1988 (Box 7)
- Interfolio (Box 8)
- Rowena Olegario-Tenure (Box 8)
- A+S Faculty Council (Box 8)
- Curriculular Reform (Box 8)
- History 200-Syllabi (Box 8)
- Program of Graduate Study (Box 8)
- Graduate Admissions (Box 8)
- Graduate Program-Grants (Box 8)
- Graduate Admissions (Box 8)
- SACS Self-Assessment Summer 2008 (History, Economics + History) (Box 8)
- Undergraduate History Major (Box 8)
- Graduate Preliminary Exams (Box 8)
- Vanderbilt-Graduate Correspondence (Box 8)
- Economics + History Major (Box 8)
- History 294-Syllabus (Box 8)
- AMST 311-Intro to Southern Studies (Box 8)
- VU History Department-Minutes (Box 8)
- Secondary Appointments Committee (Box 8)
- History Department Planning (Box 8)
- Vanderbilt History Department -Memos (Box 8)
- Tenure + Promotion Guidelines (Box 8)
- Af.Am Search (Box 8)
- Promotion + Tenure Guidelines (Box 8)
- VU Faculty Senate (Box 8)
- Nashville Battlefield Monuments (Box 8)
- Museum of the New South, Charlotte (Box 8)
- Center for the Study of the American South (Box 8)
- Southern Cultures (Box 8)
- Historians of the American South (Box 8)
- SIHC (Box 8)
- Curriculum Vitae (Box 8)
- Unlabeled (Box 8)
- Library Committee 1986-87-History Herwwig (Chair), Wcislo,Eakin,Carlton (Box 8)
- Library Committee (Box 8)
- Library Committee (Box 8)
- Library Reservations Committee (Box 8)
- VU Computing (Box 8)
- History Webpages (Box 8)
- H-Net (Box 8)
- Jupiter Entertainment-History of Textile Industry (Box 8)
- American Studies Committee (Box 8)
- Summers/Pascoe/McKinley Proposal (Box 8)
- Carlton Capital Mobilization... (Box 8)
- Carlton The Revolution From Above... (Box 8)
- Carlton The "Colonial Economy" and the Postellum South: A Reappraisal (Box 8)
- Carlton The State and the Worker in the South: A Lesson From South Carolina (Box 8)
- Other Publications (Box 8)
- Reviews of Mill and Town (Box 8)
- VII. Teaching Materials Carlton (Box 8)
- Publishers' Notes, Readers' Reports, Ford Acknowl. (Box 8)
- Carlton Chapter 3-Strategies of Development (Box 8)
- Carlton Unbalanced Growth. (Box 8)
- Woodward, "W.V. Cash" (NPR Version) (Box 8)
- Steven Watts, "The Industry of American Studies" (Box 8)
- Thomas L. Stokes "Carpetbaggers of Industry" (Box 8)
- Southern Partisan Interview with Kenneth Cribb (Box 8)
- Thedo Skocol, "What Tocqueville Missed" (Box 8)
- Southern Economics Development-Clippings (Box 8)
- Roger Rosenblalt on Tobacco Execs. NYT Mag, March 20, 1994 (Box 8)
- Rodgers, "Tradition, Modernity + the American Industrial Worker" (Box 8)
- V.M.W.-Pittston Strike (Box 8)
- Paul Pickrell, "Vanity Fair in America: The House of Mirth + GWTU (Box 8)
- National Humanities Center-"The Future of the South" (Box 8)
- Thomas Nost, "Christmas Eve" (Box 8)
- Honea Path Memorial-Dedication (Box 8)
- Conference on the Writing of Regional History in the South (Box 9)
- Vanderbilt History 115w: What is a Southerner (Box 9)
- Vanderbilt History 295: From Old South to New (Box 9)
- Vanderbilt History 295: From Old South to New (Box 9)
- Edward L. Ayers (Box 10)
- Lewis Baldwin (Box 10)
- Bess Beatty Promotion Review (Box 10)
- Lewis Bellardo (Box 10)
- Barbara Bellows (Box 10)
- Bill bemberger (Box 10)
- Bess Beatty (Box 10)
- Michael Bess (Box 10)
- Merle Black (Box 10)
- Howard Boorman (Box 10)
- Shearer Davis Bowman (Box 10)
- Peter Brush (Box 10)
- Walter L. Buenger (Box 10)
- Vernon Burton-Urbana, Ill. (Box 10)
- Burton-McMath Project (Box 10)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Bill Caferro (Box 10)
- Milton Camtor (Box 10)
- Joyce Chaplin (Box 10)
- James C. Cobb (Box 10)
- Peter Coclanis (Box 10)
- Coclania-II (Box 10)
- Mike Crawford (Box 10)
- Charles Delzell (Box 10)
- W. Calvin Dickinson (TN Tech) (Box 10)
- Susaan Donaldson (Box 10)
- Tom Downey (Box 10)
- Don H. Doyle (Box 10)
- Don H. Doyle (Box 10)
- Marshall Eakin (Box 10)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Laura Edwards (Box 10)
- Stanley Engerman (Box 10)
- William Erwin (Box 10)
- Adam Fairclough (Box 10)
- Drew Faust (Box 10)
- Devin Fergus (Box 10)
- Low Ferleger (Box 10)
- Barbara Fields (Box 10)
- Leon Fink (Box 10)
- Lacy K. Ford (Box 10)
- Ford-II (Box 10)
- Ford-III (Box 10)
- Roy Arsenault (Box 10)
- Chapter 1-1st Draft zerox, w revisions (Box 11)
- Chapter 2-1st Draft w revision (Box 11)
- Chapter VI (Revised) (Box 11)
- Chapter IV (Revised) (Box 11)
- Chapter V (Revised) (Box 11)
- Degree Petition, etc. (Box 11)
- "Mill + Town"-1st draft MSSS (Box 11)
- Chesnut Diary Project (Box 11)
- W.V.Snyder, "The Cotton Mill Problem" (Box 11)
- R. Wright Spears-Bibliography (Box 11)
- Greenville Club Rolls (Box 11)
- Southern Labor Studies Association (Box 11)
- S.C. Council on Human Relations-Labor Items (Box 11)
- McMath, "Durkheim, Marx, + Dixie" (Box 11)
- Southern Labor History-Bibliog. (Box 11)
- National Endowment for thhe Humanities (Box 11)
- Prospectus (Box 11)
- Abstract-Title Page (Box 11)
- Essay on Sources (Revised) (Box 11)
- Chapter 3-1st draft, w comments by CVW (Box 11)
- Chapter 4-1st draft copy with revisions (Box 11)
- 1st Draft-Ch.5-copy (Box 11)
- Chapter III-Notes + Draft (Box 11)
- Chapter IV -Notes + Draft (Revised) (Box 11)
- Introduction (revised) (Box 11)
- Chapter 1 (Revised) (Box 11)
- Chapter 2 (revised) (Box 11)
- Front matter (Box 11)
- Mill and Town - Maps (Box 11)
- Mill + Town - Permissions (Box 11)
- Dedication - Acknowledgements (Box 11)
- Dissertation - Copyright (Box 11)
- Essay on Sources (Box 11)
- Dissertation-Evaluation (Box 11)
- "Mill + Town": In-Progress Summary (Box 11)
- Prospectus (Mill + Town) (Box 11)
- Essay on Sources-Draft (Revised) (Box 11)
- Introduction (Revised) Notes + Draft (Box 11)
- Chapter One (Revised)-Notes + Draft (Box 11)
- Chapter Two (Revised)-Notes + Draft (Box 11)
- Chapter V (Revised)-Notes + Draft (Box 11)
- Chapter VI (Revised)-Notes + Draft (Box 11)
- Appendix (Box 11)
- Bedford/St.Martins (Box 11)
- Bedford/St.Martins (Box 11)
- Unlabeled (Box 12)
- Louis M. Kyriakoudes (Box 12)
- Unlabeled (Box 12)
- Unlabeled (Box 12)
- Unlabeled (Box 12)
- Frank R. Freemon (Box 12)
- Tom Franzmann (Box 12)
- Unlabeled (Box 12)
- Economic History Association - 1998 Meeting Program Committee (Box 13)
- Economic History Association (Box 13)
- Economic + Business Historical Society (Box 13)
- Cooleemee (Box 13)
- "Unbalanced Growth" Paper (Box 13)
- Unlabeled (Box 13)
- Citadel Conference, April 1985 (Box 13)
- Citadel Conference, April 1981 (Box 13)
- "Builders of a New State" Paper (Conference Version) (Box 13)
- Citadel Conference Paper - Notes + Draft (Box 13)
- Citadel Conference - April 1979 Correspondence (Box 13)
- Coastal Conference, March 1983 (Box 13)
- Business History Conference - Chapel Hill, NC, March 1999 (Box 13)
- Business History Conference (Box 13)
- Appalachian Studies Assoc - 2003 Meeting (Box 13)
- American Socioety of Church History (Box 13)
- AHA 2003 - Chicago (Box 13)
- AHA 2000 - Boston (Box 13)
- A.H.A. Sesssion, 1980 - Correspondence (Box 13)
- Alfred D. Chandler Lecture, April 2001 (Box 13)
- Univ. of S.C. - Evening Course (Box 13)
- University Of Alabama - Summersell Chair (Box 13)
- GA Tech (Box 13)
- "New Perspectives" Conference, Auburn, May 1992 (Box 13)
- American Philosophical Society (Box 13)
- American National Biography (Box 13)
- A.H.A. - Guide to Historical Literature (Box 13)
- ACLS (Box 13)
- American Council of Learned Societies (Box 13)
- "Reinventing Older Communities" Conference-Philadelphia, May 9-11, 2012 (Box 13)
- Misc. Publishers (Box 13)
- Vanderbilt Undersity Press (Box 13)
- Twayne Publications (Box 13)
- The South, the Nation, + the World - Permissions File (Box 13)
- William L. Nelson Cartographics (Maps for S/N/W) (Box 13)
- Peter Wallenstein (Box 14)
- Altina Walker (Box 14)
- Jonathan M. Wiener (Box 14)
- Mary Wingerd (Box 14)
- Donald L. Winters (Box 14)
- Woodword Correspondence (Box 14)
- Annette Cox (Box 14)
- Annette Cox Wright (Box 14)
- Gavin Wright (Box 14)
- Bertom Wyatt-Brown (Box 14)
- Yale Loans-FISL Short-term (Box 14)
- Yale Placement Service (Box 14)
- Yale Placement Service-Forms (Box 14)
- Yale Correspondence (Box 14)
- Jeffrey Young (Box 14)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 14)
- Inquiries (Box 14)
- Reggie Abbott (Box 14)
- Madeline Bell (Box 14)
- Marty Bell (Box 14)
- E.H.A. Meetin, Nashville (Box 15)
- Guggenheim Foundation (Box 15)
- Guggenheim Foundation (Box 15)
- The Historical Society (Box 15)
- The Historical Society, May 1999 (Box 15)
- Historical Society, June 2000 (Box 15)
- GA/fl Region, Historical Society-Woodward Conference, Oct. 6, 2000 (Box 15)
- Historical Society-Pauline Maier Prize (Box 15)
- The Historical Society Meeting 2004-Boothbay Harbor, ME (Box 15)
- Institute for Southern Studies (Box 15)
- International Business History Conference-Glasgow, 4-6 July 1997 (Box 15)
- "Memory" Conference (Box 15)
- Mill Village Visions Summit, April 2006 (Box 15)
- National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 15)
- National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 15)
- National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 15)
- NEH Travel Grant (Box 15)
- NEH-SCDAH Grant Review (Box 15)
- N.E.H.-S.C.H.S. Review (Box 15)
- NEH Travel Grant (Box 15)
- NEH (Box 15)
- National Humanities Center (Box 15)
- National Humanities Center (Box 15)
- National Humanities Center-Weekly Bulletins (Box 15)
- NINCH Building Blocks Conference (Box 15)
- National Humanities Center (Box 15)
- O.A.H. Meeting-Philadelphia, April 1987 (Box 15)
- O.A.H. Meeting (Box 15)
- Organization of American Historians-2000 Meeting (Box 15)
- O.A.H.-San Jones (Box 15)
- "Our Past Before Us" Conference-Clemson + Furman, March 2007 (Box 15)
- "Post-Plantation South" Seminar (Box 15)
- George C. Rogers Conference (Box 15)
- O.A.H.-2004 Meeting (Box 15)
- Reynolds Conference (Box 15)
- St. George Tucker Society Meeting, Atlanta, August 1992 (Box 15)
- St. George Tucker Society (Box 15)
- St. George Tucker Society-Annual Meeting, June 1994 (Box 15)
- John D. Roy-zerox order (Box 16)
- Stewart -Gullah Project - Sept. 77 (Box 16)
- V.S.C.-Memos (Box 16)
- Burroughs + Collins Archives (Box 16)
- Unlabeled (Box 16)
- Course Evaluations (Box 16)
- Unlabeled (Box 16)
- TTU-Memos (Box 16)
- TTU Faculty Senate (Box 16)
- History 201G-Syllabus (Box 16)
- History 201N-Syllabus (Box 16)
- USC-CCC Faculty Manual (Box 16)
- History 202-Syllabus (Box 16)
- TTU History Department Memos (Box 16)
- History 232-Tests (Box 16)
- History 202-Tests (Box 16)
- History 231-Enrollment (Box 16)
- History 231-Syllabus (Box 16)
- History 232-Syllabus (Box 16)
- History 232-Enrollment (Box 16)
- History 201-Tests (Box 16)
- History 231-Tests (Box 16)
- History 232-16 David Carlton (Box 16)
- David Carlton History 231-22 (Box 16)
- David Carlton History 232-21 (Box 16)
- David Carlton History 231-19 (Box 16)
- Carlton History 232-17 Fall (Box 16)
- Carlton History 232-14 Fall (Box 16)
- Mr. Carlton History 231-42 Fall (Box 16)
- Mr. Carlton History 231-39 Fall (Box 16)
- David Lee Carlton (Box 16)
- Job Letters (Box 16)
- Job Letters (Box 16)
- Job Letters (Box 16)
- Job Letters (Box 16)
- Job Letters (Box 16)
- Job Letters (Box 16)
- Franklin Institute (Box 16)
- College of Charlston (Box 16)
- St. Andrews Presbyterion College (Box 16)
- Southern Historical Collection (Box 16)
- Winthrop College (Box 16)
- Texas Tech University (Box 16)
- U.S.C.-Coastal Carolina College (Box 16)
- University of South Alabama (Box 16)
- Jobs-Information (Box 16)
- Baker Library (Florence Bartoshesky Lathrop) (Box 17)
- Duke University Library (Box 17)
- Library of Congress (Box 17)
- S.C. Dept. of Archives + history (Box 17)
- South Caroliniana Library (Box 17)
- Southern Baptist Historical Library + Archives (Box 17)
- Alabama Review (Box 17)
- American Historical Review (Box 17)
- Annals of Iowa (Box 17)
- Business History Review (Box 17)
- Canadian Review of American Studies (Box 17)
- Challenge (Box 17)
- Civil War History (Box 17)
- Enterprise and Society (Box 17)
- Georgia Historical Quarterly (Box 17)
- The Historian (Box 17)
- Industrial + Labor Relations Review (Box 17)
- Journal of American History (Box 17)
- JAH-"Revolution From Above" Correspondence (Box 17)
- Journal of Economic History (Box 17)
- Journal of Interdisciplinary History (Box 17)
- Journal of S.W. Georgia History (Box 17)
- Journal of Urban History (Box 17)
- Labor History (Box 17)
- North Carolina Historical Review (Box 17)
- Social Forces (Box 17)
- FRB of Richmon - Region Focus (Box 17)
- Reviews in American History (Box 17)
- South Carolina Historical Magazine (Box 17)
- Southern Communities (Box 17)
- Southern Cultures (Box 17)
- "To The Land" (Box 17)
- Unlabeled (Box 17)
- Misc. Journals (Box 17)
- Addision Wesley Longman (Box 17)
- Bedford Book/St. Martins Press (Box 17)
- Blackwell's (Box 17)
- Cambridge University Press (Box 17)
- D.C. Heath + Co (Box 17)
- Encyclopedia of the Confederacy (Box 17)
- Alfred A. Knopf, Inc. (Box 17)
- LSU Press (Box 17)
- LSU Press (Box 17)
- LSU Press (Box 17)
- McGraw-Hill, Inc. (Box 17)
- Mississippi Quarterly (Box 17)
- University of Missouri Press (Box 17)
- Oxford University Press (Box 17)
- Prentice-Hall, Inc. (Box 17)
- Rutgers Unviersity Press (Box 17)
- University Press of Florida (Box 17)
- University of Georgia Press (Box 17)
- "Global Perspectives" Volume University of Missouri Press (Box 17)
- UNC Press-Chapel Hill (Box 17)
- University of South Carolina Press (Box 17)
- University of Tennessee Press (Box 17)
- Univ. Press of Virginia (Box 17)
- SHA 2004-Memphis (Box 18)
- Report Session Proposal-SHA '95 (Box 18)
- SIP-SHA Session (Box 18)
- SIHC (Box 18)
- SHA 2011-Baltimore (Box 18)
- SIHC, February 2002 (Box 18)
- Southern Labor Studies Conference (Box 18)
- Southern Labor Studies Conference (Box 18)
- Southern Oral History Program (Box 18)
- Southern Regional Council (Box 18)
- Southern Regional Education Board (Box 18)
- Woodrow Wildon Center (Box 18)
- Southern Sociological Society, April 1998 (Box 18)
- Tennesse Arts Commission (Box 18)
- Tennessee Conference of Historians (Box 18)
- Tennessee Conference of Historians, 1995, 1996 (Box 18)
- Triangle Economics History Workshop (Box 18)
- University South Caroliniana Society (Box 18)
- VU Economics Policy Workshops-David Wildasin (Box 18)
- Letters to the Editor (Box 18)
- Resume' (Box 18)
- Tenure (Box 18)
- Leave of Absence, Spring 1991 (Box 18)
- Leave of Absence (Box 18)
- Leave of Absence, Spring 1999 (Box 18)
- Z-Star EX (Box 18)
- Horry Telephone Group (Box 18)
- Amherst Reunion Talk (Box 18)
- Anderson paper (AHA)-Draft (Box 18)
- E.H. Beardsley-Spring Symposium (Box 18)
- "Builders" Paper (Extended Version) Notes + Draft (Box 18)
- "Builders of a New State" Paper (Expanded version) (Box 18)
- Old South to New-Correspondence (Box 18)
- "Commercial Expositions" (Box 18)
- Companion to Southern Literature (Box 18)
- Consortium on 1934 Strike (Box 18)
- Dictionary of Literary Biography (Box 18)
- Merle Curtis-DLB (Box 18)
- "Reinhold Niebuhr" (Box 18)
- Dictionary of N.C. Biography (Box 18)
- Encyclopedia of American Studies (Box 18)
- Encyclopedia of Slavery (Box 18)
- Encyclopedia of Social History (Box 18)
- Encyclopedia of Southern Culture (Box 18)